<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
	<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
		<MASTER_PAD_VERSION>3.11</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
		<MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>PADGen 3.1.1.50 http://www.padgen.org</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
		<MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://pad.asp-software.org</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
	</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
	<Company_Info>
		<Company_Name>Borderline Software, Inc.</Company_Name>
		<Address_1>1216 N. Parkway Drive</Address_1>
		<Address_2 />
		<City_Town>Pekin</City_Town>
		<State_Province>IL</State_Province>
		<Zip_Postal_Code>61615</Zip_Postal_Code>
		<Country>USA</Country>
		<Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.borderlinesoftware.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
		<Contact_Info>
			<Author_First_Name>Brian</Author_First_Name>
			<Author_Last_Name>Patterson</Author_Last_Name>
			<Author_Email>b.patterson@borderlinesoftware.com</Author_Email>
			<Contact_First_Name>Brian</Contact_First_Name>
			<Contact_Last_Name>Patterson</Contact_Last_Name>
			<Contact_Email>b.patterson@borderlinesoftware.com</Contact_Email>
		</Contact_Info>
		<Support_Info>
			<Sales_Email>b.patterson@borderlinesoftware.com</Sales_Email>
			<Support_Email>b.patterson@borderlinesoftware.com</Support_Email>
			<General_Email>b.patterson@borderlinesoftware.com</General_Email>
			<Sales_Phone />
			<Support_Phone />
			<General_Phone />
			<Fax_Phone />
		</Support_Info>
	</Company_Info>
	<Program_Info>
		<Program_Name>DevGrep</Program_Name>
		<Program_Version>1.8.238</Program_Version>
		<Program_Release_Month>05</Program_Release_Month>
		<Program_Release_Day>23</Program_Release_Day>
		<Program_Release_Year>2013</Program_Release_Year>
		<Program_Cost_Dollars>9.99</Program_Cost_Dollars>
		<Program_Cost_Other_Code />
		<Program_Cost_Other />
		<Program_Type>Shareware</Program_Type>
		<Program_Release_Status>Minor Update</Program_Release_Status>
		<Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
		<Program_OS_Support>Win2000,Win7 x32,Win7 x64,Win98,WinServer,WinVista,WinVista x64,WinXP</Program_OS_Support>
		<Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
		<Program_Change_Info>A few updates to the indexed search as well as some bug fixes to the internal editor.</Program_Change_Info>
		<Program_Specific_Category>Utilities</Program_Specific_Category>
		<Program_Category_Class>System Utilities::File &amp; Disk Management</Program_Category_Class>
		<Program_System_Requirements />
		<File_Info>
			<File_Size_Bytes>1803904</File_Size_Bytes>
			<File_Size_K>1761</File_Size_K>
			<File_Size_MB>1.72</File_Size_MB>
		</File_Info>
		<Expire_Info>
			<Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
			<Expire_Count />
			<Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
			<Expire_Other_Info />
			<Expire_Month />
			<Expire_Day />
			<Expire_Year />
		</Expire_Info>
	</Program_Info>
	<Program_Descriptions>
		<English>
			<Keywords>Search,Grep,Edit,Usage</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>File search/edit including duplicate files</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>File search and edit including duplicate file finder.</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>DevGrep - intended mainly for software developers but provides benefits to almost any user.  DevGrep is capable of searching thousand of files per second. Search results are displayed in a clear and concise format.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>DevGrep - intended mainly for software developers but provides benefits to almost any user.  DevGrep is capable of searching thousand of files per second. Search results are displayed in a clear and concise format including the file that the match was found in, the folder where the file is located, the type of file, the number of matches found and the size of the file. Click on a match and DevGrep will show a preview of the file/matches within it</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>DevGrep - the best damn Search and Editor intended mainly for software developers but provides benefits to almost any user.  DevGrep is capable of searching thousand of files per second. Search results are displayed in a clear and concise format including the file that the match was found in, the folder where the file is located, the type of file, the number of matches found and the size of the file. Click on a match and DevGrep will show a preview of the file and matches within in.

* Display matches within a file and have DevGrep display n lines before the matches text and n lines following the matched text.
* Open a file using the build in syntax highlighting text editor or have it open in your favorite editor.
* Search in current search results. Perform a search and then search again within those results to filter down what you may be looking for.
* Perform a replace within files or search results. Replacements can be anything from a single word or letter to multiple lines. Replace using Regular Expressions.
* Search using standard text or Regular Expressions.
* Choose the file extensions that should be searched from the extensive list or add your own.
* Print search results for a single file or a compiled list of all search results.
* Export search results to HTML or CSV. (RTF and Text coming soon)
* Search all files or search using indexes. DevGrep can generate an index for files on your computer which allows it to search 100,000 files in only a few seconds. Update the index on demand or schedule this index to update at a scheduled time.
* Scan your system for duplicate files. You can then remove all duplicates. The duplicate file scanner includes "file groups" such as Images, Music, Videos etc. You may also add your own file types.
* Visualize search results in a Treemap display.
* Visualize disk usage in a Treemap. See what folders are using the most space and drill down in to those results to get to the bottom of your shrinking drive space.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</English>
	</Program_Descriptions>
	<Web_Info>
		<Application_URLs>
			<Application_Info_URL>http://www.borderlinesoftware.com/products/products-windows/product-devgrep</Application_Info_URL>
			<Application_Order_URL>http://www.borderlinesoftware.com/products/products-windows/product-devgrep</Application_Order_URL>
			<Application_Screenshot_URL>http://www.borderlinesoftware.com/Software/Installs/DevGrep/MainInterface.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
			<Application_Icon_URL>http://www.borderlinesoftware.com/Software/Installs/DevGrep/DevGrep.png</Application_Icon_URL>
			<Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.borderlinesoftware.com/Software/Installs/DevGrep/DevGrep.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
		</Application_URLs>
		<Download_URLs>
			<Primary_Download_URL>http://www.borderlinesoftware.com/Software/Installs/DevGrep/InstallDevGrep.exe</Primary_Download_URL>
			<Secondary_Download_URL />
			<Additional_Download_URL_1 />
			<Additional_Download_URL_2 />
		</Download_URLs>
	</Web_Info>
	<Permissions>
		<Distribution_Permissions>DevGrep may be freely distributed as long as the name of the original installation file and license information are not modified.</Distribution_Permissions>
		<EULA>DevGrep SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT

SOFTWARE LICENSE AGREEMENT
This Software License Agreement ("Agreement") is made and effective this day by and between Brian D. Patterson ("Developer") and you ("Licensee").

Developer has developed and licenses to users its software program marketed under the name DevGrep (the "Software").

Licensee desires to utilize a copy of the Software.

NOW, THEREFORE, in consideration of the mutual promises set forth herein, Developer and Licensee agree as follows:

1. License.
Developer hereby grants to Licensee a perpetual, non-exclusive, limited license to use the Software in the United States of America as set forth in this Agreement.

2. Restrictions.
Licensee shall not modify, copy, duplicate, reproduce, license or sublicense the Software, or transfer or convey the Software or any right in the Software to anyone else without the prior written consent of Developer; provided that Licensee may make one copy of the Software for backup or archival purposes. 

3. Fee.
In consideration for the grant of the license and the use of the Software, Licensee agrees to pay Developer. The Software can be used for a trial period to evaluate the functionality but a license should be purchased from the Developer on or before the trial software has expire.

4. Warranty of Title.
Developer hereby represents and warrants to Licensee that Developer is the owner of the Software or otherwise has the right to grant to Licensee the rights set forth in this Agreement. In the event any breach or threatened breach of the foregoing representation and warranty, Licensee's sole remedy shall be to require Developer or to either: i) procure, at Developer's expense, the right to use the Software, ii) replace the Software or any part thereof that is in breach and replace it with Software of comparable functionality that does not cause any breach, or iii) refund to Licensee the full amount of the license fee upon the return of the Software and all copies thereof to Developer.

5. Warranty of Functionality.
A. The Developer assumes no responsibility for any damage that may be cause to any system as a result of using the Software.

B. In the event of any defect in the media upon which the Software is provided arising within 7 days of the date of delivery of the Software, upon return to Developer of the Software upon the original media, Developer shall provide Licensee a new copy of the Software.

6. Software Maintenance.
A. Standard maintenance. During the Warranty Period, Developer shall provide to Licensee any new, corrected or enhanced version of the Software as created by Developer. Such enhancement shall include all modifications to the Software which increase the speed, efficiency or ease of use of the Software, or add additional capabilities or functionality to the Software, but shall not include any substantially new or rewritten version of the Software. Software maintenance is only provided for the same Major version of software that Licensee owns a license for.

B. Optional maintenance. After expiration of the Warranty Period, Licensee may continue to receive maintenance support for successive twelve (12) month periods. The charge for such optional maintenance support shall be Developer's regular list price for maintenance and support for the Software as published from time to time by Developer. Licensor shall notify Developer in writing if it desires to receive optional maintenance. If Licensee fails to take optional maintenance and later elects to receive it, Developer reserves the right to charge Licensee its maintenance fees for the period of the lapse in maintenance. Developer may elect to discontinue maintenance at any time upon notice to Licensee, and refund of any then unearned maintenance fees.

7. Payment.
Payment of the license fee shall be made upon delivery of the Software. Payment of any other amount owed by Licensee to Developer pursuant to this Agreement shall be paid within thirty (30) days following invoice from Developer. In the event any overdue amount owed by Licensee is not paid following ten (10) days written notice from Developer, then in addition to any other amount due, Developer may impose and Licensee shall pay a late payment charge at the rate of none percent (9%) per month on any overdue amount.

8. Taxes.
In addition to all other amounts due hereunder, Licensee shall also pay to Developer, or reimburse Developer as appropriate, all amounts due for property tax on the Software and for sales, use, excise taxes or other taxes which are measured directly by payments made by Licensee to Developer. In no event shall Licensee be obligated to pay any tax paid on the income of Developer or paid for Developer's privilege of doing business.

9. Warranty Disclaimer.
DEVELOPER'S WARRANTIES SET FORTH IN THIS AGREEMENT ARE EXCLUSIVE AND ARE IN LIEU OF ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.

10. Limitation of Liability.
Developer shall not be responsible for, and shall not pay, any amount of incidental, consequential or other indirect damages, whether based on lost revenue or otherwise, regardless of whether Developer was advised of the possibility of such losses in advance. In no event shall Developer's liability hereunder exceed the amount of license fees paid by Licensee, regardless of whether Licensee's claim is based on contract, tort, strict liability, product liability or otherwise.

11. Notice.
Any notice required by this Agreement or given in connection with it, shall be in writing and shall be given to the appropriate party by personal delivery or by certified mail, postage prepaid, or recognized overnight delivery services.


    If to Developer:
    Brian D. Patterson
    Borderline Software, Inc.
    9905 N. Garden lane
    Peoria, IL 61615

12. Governing Law.
This Agreement shall be construed and enforced in accordance with the laws of the state of Illinois.

13. No Assignment.
Neither this Agreement nor any interest in this Agreement may be assigned by Licensee without the prior express written approval of Developer.

14. Final Agreement.
This Agreement terminates and supersedes all prior understandings or agreements on the subject matter hereof. This Agreement may be modified only by a further writing that is duly executed by both parties.

15. Severability.
If any term of this Agreement is held by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid or unenforceable, then this Agreement, including all of the remaining terms, will remain in full force and effect as if such invalid or unenforceable term had never been included.

16. Headings.
Headings used in this Agreement are provided for convenience only and shall not be used to construe meaning or intent.


Borderline Software, Inc.
(DevGrep is a registered trademark of Brian D. Patterson)</EULA>
	</Permissions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
